dealmarkaz.pk 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - DealMarkaz.pk

* * *

Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to respecting the privacy of our customers and others and handling your personal information in accordance to the most secure and safest standards. 

**Collection of Personal Information:**

The Site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address) and demographic information such as address, telephone number and other information that is used by us to provide services. We use the customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information that he or she has requested regarding the Site or regarding services offered by us.

We use third-party advertising companies like Google to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information, specifically for Google, [click here to read the ad serving policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

**Disclosure of Personal Information:**

We may disclose certain personal information as follows:

  * by publishing ads either online and/or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers
  * to third-party websites and publishers so ads (or the content of the ads) published on DealMarkaz.pk can also be published on a broader array of venues or information vehicles,
  * to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or
  * to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.
  * by having your mobile number listed on DealMarkaz.pk, you agree to receive SMS from users who may wish to contact you through the site.

Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.

**Cookies and IP Addresses:**

When you use our website, we and our service providers may place cookies (data files on your computer, phone or mobile device's drive) or web beacons (electronic images that are placed in a web page's the code) or similar technologies. We use cookies to help us identify you as a user, to provide you a better experience on our Website, to measure promotional effectiveness and to ensure trust and safety on our Website.

Copyright © 2019 **DealMarkaz.pk** \- All Rights Reserved.
